New York State Department of State Bureau of Miscellaneous Records Enrolled Acts of the State Legislature
New York State Archives
Enrolled acts of the State Legislature
1778-2018
This series contains the original, signed and engrossed acts passed by the State Legislature beginning in the year 1778. Each law contains the text of the bill, the signatures of the speaker of the Assembly, president of the Senate, and the governor with date signed. The reverse of the final page lists chapter number, a short title, and signature of the secretary of state and date to will become law.
New York (State). Department of State. Bureau of Miscellaneous Records
314 cubic feet text
New York State Archives New York State Education Department Cultural Education Center Albany, NY 12230
13036
Carrier sheet
unmediated
Restricted: Published versions are first-use copies.
Published ("Session Laws").
Chronological by year, then numerical by chapter number.
13036-10: Roughly numerical by chapter number.
Enrolled Acts of the State Legislature (1778-1829): 13036-78, Volumes 1-131 were removed from the series for preservation due to their unique historical value.
Several laws (described above) were removed from the series as part of the Freedom Train exhibit.
State Archives accession number 13036-78 covers multiple accretions originally obtained by the New York State Library (NYSL) from 1920 through 1978. These NYSL accessions were transferred in bulk to the New York State Archives in 1978. Accession 13036-78 covers Volumes 1-1197 of the series.
13036-10: This accretion consists of original copies of laws passed in 1977 that were inadvertently cancelled by the Department of State by slicing each sheet diagonally from corner to corner. The sheets remain severed.
A0212
Series A0212, Original Colonial Laws, is a predecessor series
A3303
Series A3303, Record of Laws, is a transcription of the laws of New York for 1777-1802
A0453
Series A0453, Deeds, contains recorded copies of academy charters granted by the Board of Regents prior to 1847
17261
Series 17261, Charters and amendments, contains recorded copies of Regents charters after 1847
Published "Sessions Laws" contain indexes. Also: General Index to the Laws of the State of New York, 1777-1901 (Archie E. Baxter, 1902).
This series contains the original, signed and engrossed acts passed by the State Legislature beginning in the year 1778. Each engrossed and signed law contains the text of the bill, the signatures of the speaker of the Assembly and president of the Senate with dates of passage in each house, and the signature of the governor with date signed. On the reverse of the final page is an endorsement, giving the chapter number, a short title, and signature of the secretary of state with certification that the bill became a law on the specified date.
Several notable laws in the series were removed as part of the Freedom Train Exhibit, which traveled the state from January 1949 to February 1950: 1) "An Act for the Gradual Aboliton of Negro Slavery in New York" (L. 1799, Ch. 62), which provided that after July 4, 1799, every child born of slave parents in New York State should be free.
2) New York's Civil Service Law (May 4, 1883) was the first state statute of its kind. Theodore Roosevelt headed the assembly committee that introduced the bill, and Governor Grover Cleveland signed it.
3) A law of March 6, 1801 (Chapter 15) incorporated the Albany Mechanics Society, which was open to mechanics or tradesmen resident in Albany or its vicinity. The society was founded to protect and support members who needed help because of sickness or accident, to relieve the widows and orphans of members who died in indigent circumstances, and to provide instruction for their children.
4) The first railroad in the state, the Mohawk and Hudson Railroad, was chartered by a law of April 17, 1826 (Chapter 253). It began operation in 1831 and was the first link in what became the New York Central system.
5) Among the original laws of 1793 was one incorporating the Society for Promotion of Agriculture, Arts and Manufactures, New York's first agricultural society (and fifth in the country). The society was organized in 1791; among its purposes was to stress the value of the experimental method to improve agriculture.
6) Cornell University was chartered by the legislature on April 27, 1865, to teach branches of learning related to agriculture and the mechanical arts, including military tactics, in order to promote education of the "industrial classes." As a land grant college, it received income from the sale of lands donated to the state by the federal government under the first Morrill Act (July 2, 1862). Other qualifications being equal, preference was given to sons of those who had died in military service.
7) Chapter 753 of the Laws of 1949 stated that admission to any post-secondary educational institution chartered or incorporated by the State Board of Regents could not be denied because of race, color, religion, creed, or national origin.
13036-18: This accretion consists of two color reproductions of the act of the New York State Legislature ratifying amendments to the United State Constitution in 1790 (the "Bill of Rights). An attached certification by a representative of the Archivist of the United States attests to the authenticity of the reproduction.
Legislation; New York (State); Recording laws; Legislating; Law; Laws; New York (State)--Politics and government; New York (State). Department of State. Division of Corporations and State Records; New York (State). Legislature
Detailed Description
- Original Laws 1999 Chapters 1-115, 13036-07 (Box 1)
- Original Laws 1999 Chapters 116-345, 13036-07 (Box 2)
- Original Laws 1999 Chapters 346-500, 13036-07 (Box 3)
- Original Laws 1999 Chapters 501-659, 13036-07 (Box 4)
- Original Laws 2000 Chapters 1-76, 13036-07 (Box 5)
- Original Laws 2000 Chapters 77-251, 13036-07 (Box 6)
- Original Laws 2000 Chapters 252-470, 13036-07 (Box 7)
- Original Laws 2000 Chapters 471-609, 13036-07 (Box 8)
- Original Laws 2001 Chapters 1-100, 13036-07 (Box 9)
- Original Laws 2001 Chapters 101-243, 13036-07 (Box 10)
- Original Laws 2001 Chapters 244-399, 13036-07 (Box 11)
- Original Laws 2001 Chapters 400-587, 13036-07 (Box 12)
- Original Laws 2002 Chapters 1-53, 13036-07 (Box 13)
- Original Laws 2002 Chapters 54-117, 13036-07 (Box 14)
- Original Laws 2002 Chapters 118-225, 13036-07 (Box 15)
- Original Laws 2002 Chapters 226-325, 13036-07 (Box 16)
- Original Laws 2002 Chapters 326-425, 13036-07 (Box 17)
- Original Laws 2002 Chapters 426-535, 13036-07 (Box 18)
- Original Laws 2002 Chapters 536-645, 13036-07 (Box 19)
- Original Laws 2002 Chapters 646-698, 13036-07 (Box 20)
- Original Laws 2003 Chapters 1-52, 13036-07 (Box 21)
- Original Laws 2003 Chapter 53, 13036-07 (Box 22)
- Original Laws 2003 Chapters 54-55, 13036-07 (Box 23)
- Original Laws 2003 Chapters 55-117, 13036-07 (Box 24)
- Original Laws 2003 Chapters 118-210, 13036-07 (Box 25)
- Original Laws 2003 Chapters 211-315, 13036-07 (Box 26)
- Original Laws 2003 Chapters 316-414, 13036-07 (Box 27)
- Original Laws 2003 Chapters 415-512, 13036-07 (Box 28)
- Original Laws 2003 Chapters 513-610, 13036-07 (Box 29)
- Original Laws 2003 Chapters 611-698, 13036-07 (Box 30)
- Original Laws 2004 Chapters 1-90, 13036-07 (Box 31)
- Original Laws 2004 Chapters 91-180, 13036-07 (Box 32)
- Original Laws 2004 Chapters 181-265, 13036-07 (Box 33)
- Original Laws 2004 Chapters 266-370, 13036-07 (Box 34)
- Original Laws 2004 Chapters 371-470, 13036-07 (Box 35)
- Original Laws 2004 Chapters 471-580, 13036-07 (Box 36)
- Original Laws 2004 Chapters 581-680, 13036-07 (Box 37)
- Original Laws 2004 Chapters 681-755, 13036-07 (Box 38)
- 2004 Line Vetos Chapters 50, 53-59, 411, Veto No. 10, 13036-07 (Box 39)
- Original Laws 2005 Chapters 1-53, 13036-07 (Box 40)
- Original Laws 2005 Chapters 54-93, 13036-07 (Box 41)
- Original Laws 2005 Chapters 94-199, 13036-07 (Box 42)
- Original Laws 2005 Chapters 200-313, 13036-07 (Box 43)
- Original Laws 2005 Chapters 314-424, 13036-07 (Box 44)
- Original Laws 2005 Chapters 425-534, 13036-07 (Box 45)
- Original Laws 2005 Chapters 535-644, 13036-07 (Box 46)
- Original Laws 2005 Chapters 645-767, 13036-07 (Box 47)
- Session Laws 1-54; Veto #1, 208.209 Concurrent Resolutions (3 for 2006), 13036-11 (Box 1)
- Session Laws 55-130, 2006; 13036-11 (Box 2)
- Session Laws 131-246, 2006; 13036-11 (Box 3)
- Session Laws 247-356, 2006; 13036-11 (Box 4)
- Session Laws 357-471, 2006; 13036-11 (Box 5)
- Session Laws 472-584, 2006; 13036-11 (Box 6)
- Session Laws 585-695, 2006; 13036-11 (Box 7)
- Session Laws 696-748, 2006; 13036-11 (Box 8)
- Session Laws 1-55, 2007; 13036-11 (Box 9)
- Session Laws 56-150, 2007; 13036-11 (Box 10)
- Session Laws 151-260, 2007; 13036-11 (Box 11)
- Session Laws 261-370, 2007; 13036-11 (Box 12)
- Session Laws 371-478, 2007; 13036-11 (Box 13)
- Session Laws 479-580, 2007; 13036-11 (Box 14)
- Session Laws 581-689; Concurrent Resolutions (5 for 2007), 13036-11 (Box 15)
- Session Laws 1-53; Concurrent Resolutions (1 for 2008), 13036-11 (Box 16)
- Session Laws 54-116, 2008; 13036-11 (Box 17)
- Session Laws 117-218, 2008; 13036-11 (Box 18)
- Session Laws 219-331, 2008; 13036-11 (Box 19)
- Session Laws 332-440, 2008; 13036-11 (Box 20)
- Session Laws 441-530, 2008; 13036-11 (Box 21)
- Session Laws 531-636, 2008; 13036-11 (Box 22)
- Session Laws 637-652, 2008; 13036-11 (Box 23)
- Session Laws 1-55, 2009; 13036-11 (Box 24)
- Session Laws 56-145, 2009; 13036-11 (Box 25)
- Session Laws 146-255, 2009; 13036-11 (Box 26)
- Session Laws 256-380, 2009; 13036-11 (Box 27)
- Session Laws 381-495, 2009; 13036-11 (Box 28)
- Session Laws 496-507; Concurrent Resolutions (2 for 2009), 13036-11 (Box 29)
- Line Vetoes 50-54/Chapter Laws, 2006; 13036-12 (Box 1)
- Line Vetoes 54-61/Chapter Laws, 2006; 13036-12 (Box 2)
- Chapter/Session Laws 1-55, 2010; 13036-12 (Box 3)
- Chapter/Session Laws 56-141, 2010; 13036-12 (Box 4)
- Chapter/Session Laws 142-270, 2010; 13036-12 (Box 5)
- Chapter/Session Laws 271-390, 2010; 13036-12 (Box 6)
- Chapter/Session Laws 391-510, 2010; 13036-12 (Box 7)
- Chapter/Session Laws 511-568 (Also includes Concurrent Resolutions for that year), 2010; 13036-12 (Box 8)
- Line Vetoes (Chapter 54) 4736-6709, 2010; 13036-12 (Box 9)
- Line Vetoes (Chapter 53) 15-2499, 2010; 13036-12 (Box 10)
- Line Vetoes (Chapter 53) 2500-4735, 2010; 13036-12 (Box 11)
- Chapter/Sessions Laws 1-53; Concurrent Resolutions, 2012; 13036-14 (Box 1)
- Chapter/Session Laws 54-140, 2012; 13036-14 (Box 2)
- Chapter/Session Laws 141-260, 2012; 13036-14 (Box 3)
- Chapter/Session Laws 261-380, 2012; 13036-14 (Box 4)
- Chapter/Session Laws 381-490, 2012; 13036-14 (Box 5)
- Chapter/Session Laws 491-505, 2012; 13036-14 (Box 6)
- Chapter/Session Laws 1-56, 2011; 13036-14A (Box 1)
- Chapter/Session Laws 57-155, 2011; 13036-14A (Box 2)
- Chapter/Session Laws 156-273, 2011; 13036-14A (Box 3)
- Chapter/Session Laws 274-375, 2011; 13036-14A (Box 4)
- Chapter/Session Laws 376-485, 2011; 13036-14A (Box 5)
- Chapter/Session Laws 486-610, 2011; 13036-14A (Box 6)
- Chapter/Session Laws 1-55, 2013; 13036-14A (Box 7)
- Chapter/Session Laws 56-150, 2013; 13036-14A (Box 8)
- Chapter/Session Laws 151-250, 2013; 13036-14A (Box 9)
- Chapter/Session Laws 251-365, 2013; 13036-14A (Box 10)
- Chapter/Session Laws 366-470, 2013; 13036-14A (Box 11)
- Chapter/Session Laws 471-558, 2013; 13036-14A (Box 12)
- Laws 1-53, 13036-15 (Box 1)
- Laws 54-107, 13036-15 (Box 2)
- Laws 108-225, 13036-15 (Box 3)
- Laws 226-340, 13036-15 (Box 4)
- Laws 341-460, 13036-15 (Box 5)
- Laws 461-552, 13036-15 (Box 6)
- Ch. 1-56, 13036-16 (Box 1)
- Ch. 57-165, 13036-16 (Box 2)
- ch. 166-285, 13036-16 (Box 3)
- ch 286-405, 13036-16 (Box 4)
- ch 406-540, 13036-16 (Box 5)
- Chapters 541-589, 13036-16 (Box 6)
- Chapters 1-50, 13036-18A (Box 1)
- Chapters 51-91, 13036-18A (Box 2)
- Chapters 92-165, 13036-18A (Box 3)
- Chapters 166-270, 13036-18A (Box 4)
- Chapters 217-380, 13036-18A (Box 5)
- Chapters 381-480, 13036-18A (Box 6)
- Chapters 481-506, 13036-18A (Box 7)
- Chapter Laws 1-54, 13036-19 (Box 1)
- Chapter Laws 55-160, 13036-19 (Box 2)
- Chapter Laws 161-300, 13036-19 (Box 3)
- Chapter Laws 301-435, 13036-19 (Box 4)
- Chapter Laws 436-522, 13036-19 (Box 5)
- Original Laws 1895 Vols. 1-4, 13036-78 (Box 1)
- Original Laws 1895 Vols. 5-8, 13036-78 (Box 2)
- Original Laws 1895 Vols. 9-12, 13036-78 (Box 3)
- Original Laws 1895 Vol. 13; 1896 Vols. 1-3, 13036-78 (Box 4)
- Original Laws 1896 Vols. 4-7, 13036-78 (Box 5)
- Original Laws 1896 Vols. 8-11, 13036-78 (Box 6)
- Original Laws 1896 Vol. 12; 1897 Vols. 1-3, 13036-78 (Box 7)
- Original Laws 1897 Vols. 4-7, 13036-78 (Box 8)
- Original Laws 1897 Vols. 8-11, 13036-78 (Box 9)
- Original Laws 1898 Vols. 1-4, 13036-78 (Box 10)
- Original Laws 1898 Vols. 5-8; 1899 Vol. 1, 13036-78 (Box 11)
- Original Laws 1899 Vols. 2-5, 13036-78 (Box 12)
- Original Laws 1899 Vols. 6-9; 1900 Vol. 1, 13036-78 (Box 13)
- Original Laws 1900 Vols. 2-5, 13036-78 (Box 14)
- Original Laws 1900 Vols. 6-8; 1901 Vol. 1, 13036-78 (Box 15)
- Original Laws 1901 Vols. 2-5, 13036-78 (Box 16)
- Original Laws 1901 Vols. 6-7; 1902 Vols. 1-2, 13036-78 (Box 17)
- Original Laws 1902 Vols. 3-5, 13036-78 (Box 18)
- Original Laws 1903 Vols. 1-4, 13036-78 (Box 19)
- Original Laws 1903 Vols. 5-7; 1904 Vol. 1, 13036-78 (Box 20)
- Original Laws 1904 Vols. 2-5, 13036-78 (Box 21)
- Original Laws 1904 Vols. 6-7; 1905 Vols. 1-2, 13036-78 (Box 22)
- Original Laws 1905 Vols. 3-5, 13036-78 (Box 23)
- Original Laws 1905 Vols. 6-8, 13036-78 (Box 24)
- Original Laws 1905 Vol. 9; 1906 Vols. 1-2, 13036-78 (Box 25)
- Original Laws 1906 Vols. 3-5, 13036-78 (Box 26)
- Original Laws 1906 Vols. 6-7; 1907 Vol. 1, 13036-78 (Box 27)
- Original Laws 1907 Vols. 2-5, 13036-78 (Box 28)
- Original Laws 1907 Vols. 6-9, 13036-78 (Box 29)
- Original Laws 1907 Vol. 10; 1908 Vols. 1-3, 13036-78 (Box 30)
- Original Laws 1908 Vols. 4-7, 13036-78 (Box 31)
- Original Laws 1909 Vols. 1-3, 13036-78 (Box 32)
- Original Laws 1909 Vols. 4-7, 13036-78 (Box 33)
- Original Laws 1909 Vols. 8-11, 13036-78 (Box 34)
- Original Laws 1909 Vol. 12; 1910 Vols. 1-3, 13036-78 (Box 35)
- Original Laws 1910 Vols. 4-5; 1911 Vol. 1, 13036-78 (Box 36)
- Original Laws 1911 Vols. 2-5, 13036-78 (Box 37)
- Original Laws 1911 Vols. 6-9, 13036-78 (Box 38)
- Original Laws 1911 Vols. 10-11; 1912 Vols. 1-2, 13036-78 (Box 39)
- Original Laws 1912 Vols. 3-6, 13036-78 (Box 40)
- Original Laws 1912 Vols. 7-10, 13036-78 (Box 41)
- Original Laws 1913 Vols. 1-3, 13036-78 (Box 42)
- Original Laws 1913 Vols. 4-6, 13036-78 (Box 43)
- Original Laws 1913 Vol. 7; 1914 Vols. 1-2, 13036-78 (Box 44)
- Original Laws 1914 Vols. 3-6, 13036-78 (Box 45)
- Original Laws 1914 Vol. 7; 1915 Vols. 1-3, 13036-78 (Box 46)
- Original Laws 1915 Vols. 4-6, 13036-78 (Box 47)
- Original Laws 1915 Vols. 7-8; 1916 Vols. 1-2, 13036-78 (Box 48)
- Original Laws 1916 Vols. 3-5, 13036-78 (Box 49)
- Original Laws 1916 Vols. 6-8, 13036-78 (Box 50)
- Original Laws 1917 Vols. 1-3, 13036-78 (Box 51)
- Original Laws 1917 Vols. 4-6, 13036-78 (Box 52)
- Original Laws 1917 Vols. 7-8; 1918 Vols. 1-2, 13036-78 (Box 53)
- Original Laws 1918 Vols. 3-5, 13036-78 (Box 54)
- Original Laws 1918 Vol. 6; 1919 Vols. 1-2, 13036-78 (Box 55)
- Original Laws 1919 Vols. 3-5, 13036-78 (Box 56)
- Original Laws 1920 Vols. 1-2, 13036-78 (Box 57)
- Original Laws 1920 Vols. 3-5, 13036-78 (Box 58)
- Original Laws 1920 Vols. 6-7, 13036-78 (Box 59)
- Original Laws 1921 Vols. 1-3, 13036-78 (Box 60)
- Original Laws 1921 Vols. 4-6, 13036-78 (Box 61)
- Original Laws 1921 Vol. 7; 1922 Vols. 1-4, 13036-78 (Box 62)
- Original Laws 1922 Vols. 5-7, 13036-78 (Box 63)
- Original Laws 1923 Vols. 1-4, 13036-78 (Box 64)
- Original Laws 1923 Vols. 5-7, 13036-78 (Box 65)
- Original Laws 1924 Vols. 1-3, 13036-78 (Box 66)
- Original Laws 1924 Vols. 4-5; 1925 Vol. 1, 13036-78 (Box 67)
- Original Laws 1925 Vols. 2-4, 13036-78 (Box 68)
- Original Laws 1926 Vols. 1-3, 13036-78 (Box 69)
- Original Laws 1926 Vols. 4-5; 1927 Vol. 1, 13036-78 (Box 70)
- Original Laws 1927 Vols. 2-5, 13036-78 (Box 71)
- Original Laws 1927 Vol. 6; 1928 Vols. 1-3, 13036-78 (Box 72)
- Original Laws 1928 Vols. 4-5, 13036-78 (Box 73)
- Original Laws 1929 Vols. 1-2, 13036-78 (Box 74)
- Original Laws 1929 Vols. 3-4, 13036-78 (Box 75)
- Original Laws 1930 Vols. 1-3, 7, 13036-78 (Box 76)
- Original Laws 1930 Vols. 4-6, 13036-78 (Box 77)
- Original Laws 1931 Vols. 1-3, 6, 13036-78 (Box 78)
- Original Laws 1931 Vols. 4-5; 1932 Vols. 2, 5, 13036-78 (Box 79)
- Original Laws 1932 Vols. 1, 3, 4, 13036-78 (Box 80)
- Original Laws 1933 Vols. 1-3, 13036-78 (Box 81)
- Original Laws 1933 Vols. 4-5; 1934 Vol. 1, 13036-78 (Box 82)
- Original Laws 1934 Vols. 2-4, 13036-78 (Box 83)
- Original Laws 1934 Vols. 5-6; 1935 Vol. 1, 13036-78 (Box 84)
- Original Laws 1935 Vols. 2-4, 13036-78 (Box 85)
- Original Laws 1935 Vols. 5-6; 1936 Vols. 1-2, 13036-78 (Box 86)
- Original Laws 1936 Vols. 3-6, 13036-78 (Box 87)
- Original Laws 1936 Vols. 7-8; 1937 Vol. 1, 13036-78 (Box 88)
- Original Laws 1937 Vols. 2-5, 13036-78 (Box 89)
- Original Laws 1937 Vols. 6-9, 13036-78 (Box 90)
- Original Laws 1938 Vols. 1-4, 13036-78 (Box 91)
- Original Laws 1938 Vols. 5-6; 1939 Vols. 1-2, 13036-78 (Box 92)
- Original Laws 1939 Vols. 3-6, 13036-78 (Box 93)
- Original Laws 1939 Vols. 7-9, 13036-78 (Box 94)
- Original Laws 1940 Vols. 1-3, 13036-78 (Box 95)
- Original Laws 1940 Vols. 4-6, 13036-78 (Box 96)
- Original Laws 1941 Vols. 1-3, 13036-78 (Box 97)
- Original Laws 1941 Vols. 4-5, 13036-78 (Box 98)
- Original Laws 1941 Vol. 6; 1942 Vols. 1-2, 13036-78 (Box 99)
- Original Laws 1942 Vols. 3-4, 13036-78 (Box 100)
- Original Laws 1942 Vols. 5-6; 1943 Vol. 1, 13036-78 (Box 101)
- Original Laws 1943 Vols. 2-3, 13036-78 (Box 102)
- Original Laws 1943 Vol. 4; 1944 Vols. 1-2, 13036-78 (Box 103)
- Original Laws 1944 Vols. 3-4, 13036-78 (Box 104)
- Original Laws 1944 Vol. 5; 1945 Vols. 1-2, 13036-78 (Box 105)
- Original Laws 1945 Vols. 3-4, 13036-78 (Box 106)
- Original Laws 1945 Vols. 5-6; 1946 Vol. 1, 13036-78 (Box 107)
- Original Laws 1946 Vols. 2-3, 13036-78 (Box 108)
- Original Laws 1946 Vols. 4-6, 13036-78 (Box 109)
- Original Laws 1947 Vols. 1-3, 13036-78 (Box 110)
- Original Laws 1947 Vols. 4-7, 13036-78 (Box 111)
- Original Laws 1948 Vols. 1-3, 13036-78 (Box 112)
- Original Laws 1948 Vols. 4-6, 13036-78 (Box 113)
- Original Laws 1949 Vols. 1-4, 13036-78 (Box 114)
- Original Laws 1949 Vols. 5-7, 13036-78 (Box 115)
- Original Laws 1950 Vols. 1-4, 13036-78 (Box 116)
- Original Laws 1950 Vols. 5-8, 13036-78 (Box 117)
- Original Laws 1951 Vols. 1-4, 13036-78 (Box 118)
- Original Laws 1951 Vols. 5-8, 13036-78 (Box 119)
- Original Laws 1951 Vol. 9; 1952 Vols. 1-3, 13036-78 (Box 120)
- Original Laws 1952 Vols. 4-7, 13036-78 (Box 121)
- Original Laws 1952 Vols. 8-9; 1953 Vols. 1-4, 13036-78 (Box 122)
- Original Laws 1953 Vols. 5-8, 13036-78 (Box 123)
- Original Laws 1953 Vols. 9-12; 1954 Vol. 1, 13036-78 (Box 124)
- Original Laws 1954 Vols. 2-5, 13036-78 (Box 125)
- Original Laws 1954 Vols. 6-8; 1955 Vol. 1, 13036-78 (Box 126)
- Original Laws 1955 Vols. 2-6, 13036-78 (Box 127)
- Original Laws 1955 Vols. 7-11, 13036-78 (Box 128)
- Original Laws 1956 Vols. 1-4, 13036-78 (Box 129)
- Original Laws 1956 Vols. 5-8, 13036-78 (Box 130)
- Original Laws 1956 Vol. 9; 1957 Vols. 1-4, 13036-78 (Box 131)
- Original Laws 1957 Vols. 5-9, 13036-78 (Box 132)
- Original Laws 1957 Vols. 10-11; 1958 Vols. 1-2, 13036-78 (Box 133)
- Original Laws 1958 Vols. 3-6, 13036-78 (Box 134)
- Original Laws 1958 Vols. 7-10, 13036-78 (Box 135)
- Original Laws 1959 Vols. 1-5, 13036-78 (Box 136)
- Original Laws 1959 Vols. 6-10, 13036-78 (Box 137)
- Original Laws 1959 Vols. 11-13; 1960 Vols. 1-2, 13036-78 (Box 138)
- Original Laws 1960 Vols. 3-7, 13036-78 (Box 139)
- Original Laws 1960 Vols. 8-11, 13036-78 (Box 140)
- Original Laws 1960 Vol. 12; 1961 Vols. 1-5, 13036-78 (Box 141)
- Original Laws 1961 Vols. 6-10, 13036-78 (Box 142)
- Original Laws 1961 Vols. 11-14; 1962 Vol. 1, 13036-78 (Box 143)
- Original Laws 1962 Vols. 2-6, 13036-78 (Box 144)
- Original Laws 1962 Vols. 7-10, 13036-78 (Box 145)
- Original Laws 1962 Vols. 11-14; 1963 Vol. 1, 13036-78 (Box 146)
- Original Laws 1963 Vols. 2-6, 13036-78 (Box 147)
- Original Laws 1963 Vols. 7-10, 13036-78 (Box 148)
- Original Laws 1963 Vols. 11-13; 1964 Vol. 1, 13036-78 (Box 149)
- Original Laws 1964 Vols. 2-5, 13036-78 (Box 150)
- Original Laws 1964 Vols. 6-9, 13036-78 (Box 151)
- Original Laws 1964 Vols. 10-11; 1965 Vols. 1-2, 13036-78 (Box 152)
- Original Laws 1965 Vols. 3-5, 13036-78 (Box 153)
- Original Laws 1965 Vols. 6-9, 13036-78 (Box 154)
- Original Laws 1966 Vols. 1-3, 13036-78 (Box 155)
- Original Laws 1966 Vols. 4-6, 13036-78 (Box 156)
- Original Laws 1966 Vols. 7-9; 1967 Vol. 1, 13036-78 (Box 157)
- Original Laws 1967 Vols. 2-5, 13036-78 (Box 158)
- Original Laws 1967 Vols. 6-8; 1968 Vol. 1, 13036-78 (Box 159)
- Original Laws 1968 Vols. 2-4, 13036-78 (Box 160)
- Original Laws 1968 Vols. 5-7, 13036-78 (Box 161)
- Original Laws 1968 Vol. 8; 1969 Vols. 1-3, 13036-78 (Box 162)
- Original Laws 1969 Vols. 4-6, 13036-78 (Box 163)
- Original Laws 1969 Vols. 7-9; 1970 Vol. 1, 13036-78 (Box 164)
- Original Laws 1970 Vols. 2-4, 13036-78 (Box 165)
- Original Laws 1970 Vols. 5-7, 13036-78 (Box 166)
- Original Laws 1970 Vols. 8-9; 1971 Vols. 1-2, 13036-78 (Box 167)
- Original Laws 1971 Vols. 3-6, 13036-78 (Box 168)
- Original Laws 1971 Vols. 7-8; 1972 Vols. 1-2, 13036-78 (Box 169)
- Original Laws 1972 Vols. 3-5, 13036-78 (Box 170)
- Original Laws 1972 Vols. 6-8; 1973 Vol. 1, 13036-78 (Box 171)
- Original Laws 1973 Vols. 2-4, 13036-78 (Box 172)
- Original Laws 1973 Vol. 5; 1974 Vols. 1-2, 13036-78 (Box 173)
- Original Laws 1974 Vols. 3-5, 13036-78 (Box 174)
- Original Laws 1974 Vol. 6; 1975 Vols. 1-3, 13036-78 (Box 175)
- Original Laws 1975 Vols. 4-7, 13036-78 (Box 176)
- Original Laws 1976 Vols. 1-3, 13036-78 (Box 177)
- Original Laws 1976 Vols. 4-6, 13036-78 (Box 178)
- Original Laws 1830 Chapters 1-85, 13036-78 (Volume 132)
- Original Laws 1830 Chapters 86-172, 13036-78 (Volume 133)
- Original Laws 1830 Chapters 173-263, 13036-78 (Volume 134)
- Original Laws 1830 Chapters 265-333 and Resolutions, 13036-78 (Volume 135)
- Original Laws 1831 Chapters 1-87, 13036-78 (Volume 136)
- Original Laws 1831 Chapters 88-174, 13036-78 (Volume 137)
- Original Laws 1831 Chapters 175-258, 13036-78 (Volume 138)
- Original Laws 1831 Chapters 259-323 and Resolutions, 13036-78 (Volume 139)
- Original Laws 1832 Chapters 1-83, 13036-78 (Volume 140)
- Original Laws 1832 Chapters 84-170, 13036-78 (Volume 141)
- Original Laws 1832 Chapters 171-254, 13036-78 (Volume 142)
- Original Laws 1832 Chapters 255-335 and Resolutions, 13036-78 (Volume 143)
- Original Laws 1833 Chapters 1-80, 13036-78 (Volume 144)
- Original Laws 1833 Chapters 81-167, 13036-78 (Volume 145)
- Original Laws 1833 Chapters 168-247, 13036-78 (Volume 146)
- Original Laws 1833 Chapters 248-323 and Resolutions, 13036-78 (Volume 147)
- Original Laws 1834 Chapters 1-140, 13036-78 (Volume 148)
- Original Laws 1834 Chapters 141-240, 13036-78 (Volume 149)
- Original Laws 1834 Chapters 241-320 and Resolutions, 13036-78 (Volume 150)
- Original Laws 1835 Chapters 1-83, 13036-78 (Volume 151)
- Original Laws 1835 Chapters 84-164, 13036-78 (Volume 152)
- Original Laws 1835 Chapters 165-239, 13036-78 (Volume 153)
- Original Laws 1835 Chapters 240-311 and Resolutions, 13036-78 (Volume 154)
- Original Laws 1836 Chapters 1-87, 13036-78 (Volume 155)
- Original Laws 1836 Chapters 88-179, 13036-78 (Volume 156)
- Original Laws 1836 Chapters 180-268, 13036-78 (Volume 157)
- Original Laws 1836 Chapters 269-536 and Resolutions, 13036-78 (Volume 158)
- Original Laws 1837 Chapters 1-126, 13036-78 (Volume 159)
- Original Laws 1837 Chapters 127-244, 13036-78 (Volume 160)
- Original Laws 1837 Chapters 245-361, 13036-78 (Volume 161)